A Guide to the John C. Watkins Papers 1979-1999
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series I-Office files 1979-1980
  - Presidential Convention SB 145 1986 (Box 17)
  - Procurement Act SB 353 1986 (Box 17)
  - Proposals 1986 (Box 17)
  - Proprietary Child Care 1986 (Box 17)
  - Radio/TV News Directors 1986 (Box 17)
  - Radioactive Waste 1986 (Box 17)
  - Registrars 1986 (Box 17)
  - Rescue Squads 1986 (Box 17)
  - Retired Federal Employees 1986 (Box 17)
  - Retirement System 1986 (Box 17)
  - Seat Belt 1986 (Box 17)
  - Self Insurance Pool SB 137 1986 (Box 17)
  - Sessions 1986 (Box 17)
  - Sex Education at School 1986 (Box 17)
  - Standards of Quality 1986 (Box 17)
  - State Colleges and Universities 1986 (Box 17)
  - The State of the Commonwealth Baliles 1986 (Box 17)
  - Stop Work Orders 1986 (Box 17)
  - Tax Exempt Schools 1986 (Box 17)
  - Taxpayers Association 1986 (Box 17)
  - Tobacco-Sales to Minors 1986 (Box 17)
  - Transportation-Va's Commission 1986 (Box 17)
  - Transfer of Development Rights HB 588 1986 (Box 17)
  - Virginia Association of Counties 1986 (Box 17)
  - Virginia Citizens Consumer Council 1986 (Box 17)
  - Virginia Tech 1986 (Box 17)
  - Victims-Bill of Rights 1986 (Box 17)
  - Vehicles-Suspension Systems Bumper Heights HB 111 1986 (Box 17)
  - Van Pools 1986 (Box 17)
  - Visually and Physically Handicapped 1986 (Box 17)
  - Water News 1986 (Box 17)
  - Wine Franchise Act 1986 (Box 17)
  - Water Project 1986 (Box 17)
  - Women's Organizations 1986 (Box 17)
  - ABC Board License-Florists 1987 (Box 18)
  - Abortions (pros and cons) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Agricultural and Forestal Act SB 580 1987 (Box 18)
  - AIDS 1987 (Box 18)
  - Amendment to Coal Bill 1987 (Box 18)
  - Annexation 1987 (Box 18)
  - Appointments 1987 (Box 18)
  - Appropriations 1987 (Box 18)
  - Agriculture Committee 1987 (Box 18)
  - Attorney General 1987 (Box 18)
  - Benefits to State and Blue Cross Subscriber HB 1396 1987 (Box 18)
  - Bill, Comments, Correspondence 1987 (Box 18)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield 1987 (Box 18)
  - Broad Street Theaters Budget Amendment 1987 (Box 18)
  - Brochure (Veterans Affair) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Brochure Correspondence (Va. Citizens Consumer Council) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Brochure Correspondence (State Agencies) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Brown Boveri 1987 (Box 18)
  - Certified Public Accountants 1987 (Box 18)
  - Charter Bills 1987 (Box 18)
  - Chief Patron Report 1987 (Box 18)
  - CHRONS 1987, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Consolidated Health Care 1987 (Box 18)
  - Clinical Psychologist Bill SB 560 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence (Department of Social Services) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence (Government Reform) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence (Tourism in Virginia) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence (Virginia Historic Landmarks) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, Bill 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, Brochures (Seat Belt Legislation) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, Brochures-Pay for Performance Program 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, Copy of Act (Va Waste Management) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, Copy of proposed bills 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence Form (Delegates or Senators) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence HB 1518 Tree Bill 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Notes (Thank you letters) 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Parental Notification 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Plantation Pipeline Company 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Proposals/Republican Caucus 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Proposal/Tax Exemption 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Proposal/Yorktown Board of Trustees 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Recreation and Parks 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Senate Bill 467 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Social Services Department 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Substance Abuse 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Summary of Legislative Positions 1987 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence-Tort Reform 1987 (Box 18)
  - Council on Human Rights SB 666 1987 (Box 18)
  - Counties, Cities, Towns Committee 1987, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Credit Card Rates 1987 (Box 18)
  - Day Care SB 514 and HB 1237 1987 (Box 18)
  - Disclosure Form 1987 (Box 18)
  - Draft Proposals 1987 (Box 19)
  - Drugs 1987 (Box 19)
  - Early Retirement Pay for Performance (Brochures, Correspondence) 1987 (Box 19)
  - Economic Development Council 1987 (Box 19)
  - Ethanol Subsidy Program SB 79 1987 (Box 19)
  - Excellence in Education 1987 (Box 19)
  - Explore Project 1987 (Box 19)
  - Family Law 1987 (Box 19)
  - Family Life Education HB 1413 1987 (Box 19)
  - Farm Bureau 1987 (Box 19)
  - Farmers Market 1987 (Box 19)
  - Firearms Preemption Bill HB 830 1987 (Box 19)
  - Flow Control HB 1155 1987 (Box 19)
  - Franchise Act HB 1165 1987 (Box 19)
  - Governor's Office 1987 (Box 19)
  - Graduation Brochure 1987 (Box 19)
  - Handicapped 1987 (Box 19)
  - Home Builders Association 1987 (Box 19)
  - Homeless 1987 (Box 19)
  - Higher Education 1987 (Box 19)
  - Issue Papers 1987 (Box 19)
  - Literary Funds 1987 (Box 19)
  - Lottery 1987 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous 1987 (Box 19)
  - Neurological Injury Comp. Act 1987 (Box 19)
  - Mass Transit 1987 (Box 19)
  - Medical College of Virginia 1987 (Box 19)
  - Medical Equipment 1987 (Box 19)
  - Mental Health 1987 (Box 19)
  - Minutes, Correspondence 1987 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous 1987 (Box 19)
  - News Release 1987 (Box 19)
  - NRA 1987 (Box 19)
  - Nursery Industry Study 1987 (Box 19)
  - Optometrists 1987 (Box 19)
  - Optometrist Correspondence 1987, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Ports 1987 (Box 19)
  - Post Labor Day School Opening 1987 (Box 19)
  - Proposals, Bills 1987, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Proposals, Summaries 1987 (Box 19)
  - Proposed 1988 Legislative Programs 1987 (Box 19)
  - Realtors 1987 (Box 19)
  - Report 1987 (Box 19)
  - Resolutions, Bills Supporting 1987 (Box 19)
  - Retail Merchants Association 1987 (Box 19)
  - Retained Funds 1987 (Box 19)
  - Rural Virginia 1987 (Box 19)
  - SCC/Corporation 1987 (Box 19)
  - Shool Board-Chesterfield 1987 (Box 19)
  - State Judgeships 1987 (Box 19)
  - States listing (appointees or elected), Correspondence 1987 (Box 19)
  - Summary, News Articles 1987 (Box 19)
  - Term Appointments 1987 (Box 19)
  - Thank You/Congratulation 1987 (Box 19)
  - Tree Bill 1987 (Box 19)
  - United Daughters of Confederacy 1987 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Coalition Against Drunk Driving 1987 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Hospital Association 1987 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Municipal League 1987 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History 1987 (Box 19)
  - Agencies on Aging 1988 (Box 20)
  - Agriculture 1988 (Box 20)
  - Agriculture on Biotechnology 1988 (Box 20)
  - All Terrain Vehicles 1988 (Box 20)
  - Annexation Laws 20
  - Alcohol (ASAP) 1988 (Box 20)
  - Birth Defects 1988 (Box 20)
  - Blue Cross and Blue Shield 1988 (Box 20)
  - Bottle Deposit Bill 1988 (Box 20)
  - Campaign Finance 1988 (Box 20)
  - Chesapeake Bay 1988 (Box 20)
  - Chesterfield County 1988 (Box 20)
  - Chesterfield County Schools 1988 (Box 20)
  - Child Support 1988 (Box 20)
  - Clean Air/Smoking 1988 (Box 20)
  - Commissioner of Accounts 1988 (Box 20)
  - Common Cause of Virginia 1988 (Box 20)
  - Community Colleges 1988 (Box 20)
  - Concealed Weapons SB 211 1988 (Box 20)
  - Constitutional Convention 1988 (Box 20)
  - Contributory Negligence 1988 (Box 20)
  - Counties, Cities and Towns HB 554 1988, 5 folders (Box 20)
  - Counties Police Departments 1988 (Box 20)
  - Covered Trucks 1988 (Box 20)
  - Coyotes SB 251 1988 (Box 20)
  - Daily Rental Equipment Taxation 1988 (Box 20)
  - Daycare HJR 306 1988 (Box 20)
  - Drugs 1988 (Box 20)
  - Elected School Boards-Fiscal Responsibility 1988 (Box 20)
  - Election Laws 1988 (Box 20)
  - Endangered Species/Budget Amendment 1988 (Box 20)
  - Erosion Control 1988 (Box 20)
  - Family Life Education Correspondence 1988 (Box 20)
  - For Your Information 1988 (Box 20)
  - Head Injury (Traumatic Brain) 1988 (Box 20)
  - Health Care 1988 (Box 20)
  - Handicapped/Disabled 1988 (Box 20)
  - Herion HB 494 1988 (Box 20)
  - Higher Education 1988 (Box 20)
  - Homeless 1988 (Box 20)
  - Housing 1988 (Box 20)
  - Hunting License 1988 (Box 20)
  - Impact Fees 1988 (Box 20)
  - Independent Insurance 1988 (Box 20)
  - Infant Mortality 1988 (Box 20)
  - Internship in State Government 1988 (Box 20)
  - Labor 1988 (Box 20)
  - Lake Genito 1988 (Box 20)
  - Land Use Tax 1988 (Box 20)
  - Landfills SB 196 1988 (Box 20)
  - Landscape Contractors (definition) 1988 (Box 20)
  - Legislation 1988 (Box 20)
  - Local Opinion Sales Tax Increase 1988 (Box 20)
  - Lottery 1988 (Box 20)
  - Magnolia Grange 1988 (Box 20)
  - Metropolitan Area Concerns 1988 (Box 20)
  - Military Dependents SB 362 1988 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous 1988 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1988 (Box 21)
  - Mopeds 1988 (Box 21)
  - Nagle, David Anthony 1988 (Box 21)
  - Narcotics Enforcement 1988 (Box 21)
  - Nontidal Wetlands HB 1037 1988 (Box 21)
  - Optional Auxiliary Grant (OAG) 1988 (Box 21)
  - Pari-Mutual Betting 1988 (Box 21)
  - Patron Reports 1988 (Box 21)
  - Pesticide Regulation 1988 (Box 21)
  - Physical Therapy HB 1024 1988 (Box 21)
  - Pound Animals HB 933 1988 (Box 21)
  - Privatization 1988 (Box 21)
  - Privileges and Elections 1988 (Box 21)
  - Psychiatric Clinical Nurse Specialist 1988 (Box 21)
  - Punitive Damages 1988 (Box 21)
  - Privileges and Elections 1988, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Proposed Legislation 1988 (Box 21)
  - Radon 1988 (Box 21)
  - Recycling Act HB 1743 1988 (Box 21)
  - Republican Caucus 1988 (Box 21)
  - Retail Sales Tax Collection 1988 (Box 21)
  - Routing State Route 288 1987 (Box 21)
  - School Board 1988 (Box 21)
  - School/Funding 1988 (Box 21)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Lobbyists) 1988 (Box 21)
  - Short Term Rental Property 1988 (Box 21)
  - Signs and Billboards, Nonconforming HB 934 1988 (Box 21)
  - Social Services 1988 (Box 21)
  - Solid Waste 1988 (Box 21)
  - SPECTRAN 1988 (Box 21)
  - Speed Limit 65 MPH 1988 (Box 21)
  - Spouses Support SB 128 1988 (Box 21)
  - State Employee Raises 1988 (Box 21)
  - State Parks 1988 (Box 21)
  - State Police Retirement 1988 (Box 21)
  - State Veterans Home 1988 (Box 21)
  - State VHRS 1988 (Box 21)
  - Statue of Repose 1988 (Box 21)
  - Status of Women 1988 (Box 21)
  - Tax Reform 1988 (Box 21)
  - Toll Collection Devices 1988 (Box 21)
  - Torte Reform Bills 1988 (Box 21)
  - Treasury Board 1988 (Box 21)
  - Tree Preservation 1988 (Box 22)
  - Tree Subcommittee 1988 (Box 22)
  - Trespassing HB 654 1988 (Box 22)
  - Unclaimed Property 1988 (Box 22)
  - UPMS 1988 (Box 22)
  - VA Chamber of Commerce 1988 (Box 22)
  - VA Inland Ports 1988 (Box 22)
  - VA Resource Authority 1988 (Box 22)
  - Violence 1988 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Education Assistance (VEA) 1988 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation 1988 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Song 1988 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Song 1988 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Tech/Budget Amendment 1988 (Box 22)
  - VSRS 1988 (Box 22)
  - Water Project, Inc. 1988 (Box 22)
  - Water Supply HB 966 1988 (Box 22)
  - 53 ft. Trailers HB 1302 1989 (Box 23)
  - Agriculture 1989 (Box 23)
  - Alcohol and Drugs (Abuse and Use) 1989 (Box 23)
  - Appointments to BDS Commissions 1989 (Box 23)
  - Banks Selling Insurance 1989 (Box 23)
  - Belytade 1989 (Box 23)
  - Brandermill Investment 1989 (Box 23)
  - Business License 1989 (Box 23)
  - Capital Projects 1989 (Box 23)
  - Certified Engineering 1989 (Box 23)
  - Chesapeake Bay and Toxic Waste 1989 (Box 23)
  - Chesterfield County 1989 (Box 23)
  - Chesterfield County Legislative Program 1989 (Box 23)
  - Chesterfield Issue Survey 1989 (Box 23)
  - Child Care 1989 (Box 23)
  - Coal 1989 (Box 23)
  - Coal and Energy Commission 1989 (Box 23)
  - Commissioner of Revenue 1989 (Box 23)
  - Computer Learning Center-Dr. Cox 1989 (Box 23)
  - Congressional Committees 1989 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence 1989, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Counselors 1989 (Box 23)
  - Counties, Cities and Towns 1989, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Courts 1989 (Box 23)
  - Delegates/Letters and Information 1989 (Box 23)
  - Drugs HB 1240 1989 (Box 23)
  - Early Childhood Development 1989 (Box 23)
  - Elected Officials Removals SB 787 1989 (Box 23)
  - Elected School Board Study 1989 (Box 23)
  - Endangered Species 1989 (Box 23)
  - Family Life 1989 (Box 23)
  - Family Life Workbook 1989 (Box 23)
  - Farm Winery 1989 (Box 23)
  - Finance Bills 1989 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Information 1989 (Box 23)
  - Grayson Commission 1989 (Box 23)
  - Grayson Commission 1989 (Box 23)
  - Guns Control SB 727 1989 (Box 23)
  - HB 115 Corporal Punishment 1989 (Box 23)
  - Health Care Service 1989 (Box 23)
  - Higher Education 1989 (Box 23)
  - Historical Preservation District HB 1913 1989 (Box 24)
  - Income Tax-Local Options 1989 (Box 24)
  - Income Tax-Reform 1989 (Box 24)
  - Impact Fees-Proffer Zoning 1989 (Box 24)
  - Instream Flow 1989 (Box 24)
  - Insurance Bills 1989 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown 4-H Center 1989 (Box 24)
  - Judicial Appointments 1989 (Box 24)
  - Land Use 1989 (Box 24)
  - Lobbyists 1989 (Box 24)
  - Local Income Tax (1%) SB 691 1989 (Box 24)
  - Lottery Proceeds 1989 (Box 24)
  - Mental Health 1989 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous 1989, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1989, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Monocan High School Band 1989 (Box 24)
  - No Heading 1989 (Box 24)
  - Nursery Inspection Fees 1989 (Box 24)
  - Parental Leave 1989 (Box 24)
  - Patron Report 1989 (Box 24)
  - Pound Animals HB 933 1989 (Box 24)
  - Powhite Parkway 1989 (Box 24)
  - Prenatal Care 1989 (Box 24)
  - Public Building Authority 1989 (Box 24)
  - Recordation Tax HB 245 1989 (Box 24)
  - Recycling 1989 (Box 24)
  - Republican Correspondence 1989 (Box 24)
  - Savings and Loans/Owning Real Estate HB 1499 1989 (Box 24)
  - Smoking HB 6014 1989 (Box 24)
  - Social Service Issues 1989 (Box 24)
  - Special Exceptions 1989 (Box 24)
  - State Employee Perspiration Plan 1989 (Box 24)
  - Survey 1989 (Box 24)
  - Tabue Station 1989 (Box 24)
  - Transfer Tax 1989 (Box 24)
  - Transferable Development Rights 1989 (Box 24)
  - Transportation Districts HB 1325 1989 (Box 24)
  - Transportation Funding 1989 (Box 24)
  - Tree Subcommittee I 1989 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Coalition Against Drunk Driving Legislative Agenda 1989 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Education Association 1989 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Housing Partnership Fund 1989 (Box 24)
  - Water Issues 1989 (Box 24)
  - Zoning 1989 (Box 24)
  - 1990 Session 1990 (Box 25)
  - Abortion/Parental Notification 1990 (Box 25)
  - Adult Homes 1990 (Box 25)
  - Agricultural 1990 (Box 25)
  - AIDS 1990 (Box 25)
  - Alcohol Abuse 1990 (Box 25)
  - Animals 1990 (Box 25)
  - Annual Reports 1990 (Box 25)
  - Appropriations 1990 (Box 25)
  - Attorney General 1990 (Box 25)
  - Attention Deficit Disorder 1990 (Box 25)
  - Banks Selling Insurance HB 335 1990 (Box 25)
  - Bills-General Letters 1990 (Box 25)
  - Binding Arbitration HJR 21 1990 (Box 25)
  - Binding Arbitration-Letters 1990 (Box 25)
  - Bliley, Tom Referrals 1990 (Box 25)
  - Blue Cross 1990 (Box 25)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield 1990 (Box 25)
  - Cash Proffers 1990 (Box 25)
  - Child Care 1990 (Box 25)
  - Clean Air Act 1990 (Box 25)
  - Cleft Palate 1990 (Box 25)
  - Clerk of the House 1990 (Box 25)
  - Comparative Negligence 1990 (Box 25)
  - Community Colleges 1990 (Box 25)
  - Constituent Colleges 1990 (Box 25)
  - Constituent Complaints 1990 (Box 25)
  - Constitutional Convention 1990 (Box 25)
  - Constitutional Offices 1990 (Box 25)
  - Contractor's Recovery Fund 1990 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence 1990, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Counties, Cities and Towns 1990 (Box 25)
  - Death Penalty 1990 (Box 25)
  - Dental Hygiene 1990 (Box 25)
  - Department of Education 1990 (Box 25)
  - Department of Health 1990 (Box 25)
  - Downzoning/Fairfax County 1990 (Box 25)
  - Elected School Boards 1990 (Box 25)
  - Engineers 1990 (Box 25)
  - Family Building Act 1990 (Box 25)
  - Flag Protection Act 1990 (Box 25)
  - Forestry 1990 (Box 25)
  - Game Wardens 1990 (Box 25)
  - Gasoline Divorcement SB 235 1990 (Box 25)
  - Gasoline Retailers 1990 (Box 25)
  - General Letters 1990 (Box 25)
  - Health Care 1990 (Box 25)
  - Heating Bills 1990 (Box 25)
  - HJR 147 (TATA) Cults 1990 (Box 25)
  - Homeless 1990 (Box 25)
  - Hunting on Prohibited Lands HB 654 1990 (Box 25)
  - Judicial Section 1990 (Box 25)
  - Legislative Program Chesterfield County 1990 (Box 25)
  - Lottery 1990 (Box 25)
  - Manufactured Housing 1990 (Box 25)
  - Meat Packing 1990 (Box 25)
  - Memorandums 1990 (Box 25)
  - Natural Gas Vehicles 1990 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous 1989 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous -unsorted 1990, 6 folders (Box 25)
  - Model General Assembly 1990 (Box 26)
  - Motor Boat Fee 1990 (Box 26)
  - Newspaper Survey 1990 (Box 26)
  - NRA 1990 (Box 26)
  - Organic Food Act/Bills 1990 (Box 26)
  - Parental Leave 1990 (Box 26)
  - Patron Reports 1990 (Box 26)
  - Personnel Act 1990 (Box 26)
  - Physical Therapy/Orthopedic Society 1990 (Box 26)
  - Population Growth and Development 1990 (Box 26)
  - Ports of Richmond 1990 (Box 26)
  - Press Releases 1990 (Box 26)
  - Prisons and Jails 1990 (Box 26)
  - Reports 1990 (Box 26)
  - Requests to John 1990 (Box 26)
  - Retirement Legislation 1990 (Box 26)
  - Route 28 1990 (Box 26)
  - Sales Tax 1990 (Box 26)
  - Senate Bill 400 1990 (Box 26)
  - Sexual Preference 1990 (Box 26)
  - Social Services 1990 (Box 26)
  - Storer Cable 1990 (Box 26)
  - Study (HJ 147, HB 1075) 1990 (Box 26)
  - Taxpayers 1990 (Box 27)
  - Thank You/Congrats 1990 (Box 27)
  - Transfer Developments Rights 1990 (Box 27)
  - Transfer Taxes 1990 (Box 27)
  - Transportation 1990 (Box 27)
  - Tuition Assistance Grant Program 1990 (Box 27)
  - VFW 1990 (Box 27)
  - Vested Rights 1990 (Box 27)
  - Vesting 1990 (Box 27)
  - Virginia Education Association 1990 (Box 27)
  - Virginia Petroleum Products Franchise Act 1990 (Box 27)
  - Virginia State Retirement System 1990 (Box 27)
  - Virginia Tech 1990 (Box 27)
  - Youth Services 1990 (Box 27)
  - Wilder 1990 (Box 27)
  - Abortion-Parental Notification 1991 (Box 28)
  - Agenda 1991 (Box 28)
  - Agriculture 1991 (Box 28)
  - Alcohol/Tobacco Abuse 1991 (Box 28)
  - Arts 1991 (Box 28)
  - Banks Selling Insurance 1991 (Box 28)
  - Banquet License 1991 (Box 28)
  - Bottle Bill 1991 (Box 28)
  - Capital Area Training Consortium 1991 (Box 28)
  - Chesapeake Bay 1991 (Box 28)
  - Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act 1991 (Box 28)
  - Chesterfield County 1991 (Box 28)
  - Chief Patron Files 1991 (Box 28)
  - Child Abuse 1991 (Box 28)
  - Clean Air Act 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence 1991 (Box 28)
  - Counties, Cities and Towns 1991 (Box 28)
  - Death Penalty/Juveniles 1991 (Box 28)
  - Direct Selling 1991 (Box 28)
  - Divorcement 1991 (Box 28)
  - Driver's License Administrative Revocation 1991 (Box 28)
  - Education 1991 (Box 28)
  - Elected School Boards 1991 (Box 28)
  - Estate Law 1991 (Box 28)
  - Fax File 1991 (Box 28)
  - Gasoline Retailers/Divorcement 1991 (Box 28)
  - Health Department 1991 (Box 28)
  - Highways 1991 (Box 28)
  - Historical Landmarks 1991 (Box 28)
  - Impact Fees 1991 (Box 28)
  - Industrial and Development Revenue Bond Act SB 178 1991 (Box 28)
  - In-Vitro Fertilization 1991 (Box 28)
  - Judges 1991 (Box 28)
  - Landfills 1991 (Box 28)
  - Legislative Summaries 1991 (Box 28)
  - Lethal Injection 1991 (Box 28)
  - Lobbyists 1991 (Box 28)
  - MCV Tuition Raise 1991 (Box 28)
  - Menus 1991 (Box 28)
  - Mechanic's Lien 1991 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous 1991, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous 1991 (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous Letters 1991 (Box 29)
  - Newsletter 1991 (Box 29)
  - Newsletter, etc. 1991 (Box 29)
  - Newspapers 1991, 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Off Track Betting 1991 (Box 29)
  - Patron and Co-Patron 1991 (Box 29)
  - Photo Radar 1991 (Box 29)
  - Physical Therapists 1991 (Box 29)
  - Prisons 1991 (Box 29)
  - Redistricting 1991 (Box 29)
  - Retired State Employees 1991 (Box 29)
  - Round Leaf Birch 1991 (Box 29)
  - Share the Ride 1991 (Box 29)
  - State Employees/Furlough 1991 (Box 29)
  - State Song 1991 (Box 29)
  - Student Letters 1991 (Box 29)
  - Thank You/Congrats 1991 (Box 29)
  - Transportation 1991 (Box 29)
  - United Way 1991 (Box 29)
  - Vaccinations 1991 (Box 29)
  - VCU 1991 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Council on Social Welfare-Legislative Package 1991 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Tech 1991 (Box 29)
  - VMI 1991 (Box 29)
  - Volunteerism 1991 (Box 29)
  - VSRS HR 987 1991 (Box 29)
  - Waste Products/Solution 1991 (Box 29)
  - YMCA 1991 (Box 29)
  - Amendments to the House Bill 30 House Appropriations Committee (Box 30)
  - Administrative Notes (Black Folder) (Box 30)
  - Attention Deficit Disorders Add Awareness Month (Box 30)
  - Budget Bill (Box 30)
  - Children Need the Support of Parents (Box 30)
  - Coal Slurry Pipelines in Virginia: A Preliminary Feasibility Study (Box 30)
  - Coal Slurry Preliminary Feasibility Report (Box 30)
  - Comparative Report of Local Government Revenues and Expenditures (Box 30)
  - Department of Military Affairs (Box 30)
  - Design Public Hearing (Box 30)
  - Design of Acts of the General Assembly of Virginia (Box 30)
  - Dictionary of Dermatological Words, Terms and Phrases (Box 30)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Statement (Box 30)
  - Executive Budget Supplement 1983 (Box 30)
  - Financing for the Future (Box 31)
  - General Assembly of Virginia Manual of the House of Delegates (Box 31)
  - Judicial Review of Local Land Use Decisions in Virginia (Box 31)
  - Location and Preliminary Design Study I (Box 31)
  - Location and Preliminary Design Study I-IV (Box 31)
  - Location Public Hearing Transcript I-II (Box 31)
  - Major Real Estate Markets in Virginia (VCU) 1984 (Box 31)
  - Major Real Estate Markets in Virginia (VCU) 1985 (Box 31)
  - Model State Prompt Pay Law (Box 31)
  - North American Marketing (Box 31)
  - Nuclear Waste Disposal (Closing the Circle) (Box 31)
  - Prompt Pay Laws are Succeeding (Box 31)
  - Prompt Pay Legislation (Box 31)
  - Proposal Grown in Virginia (Box 31)
  - Public and Private Record Repositories in Virginia A Needs Assessment Report (Box 31)
  - Report of the Department of Highways and Transportation on the Virginia Commuter Study (Box 31)
  - Report of the Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission on Working Capital Funds in Virginia (Box 31)
  - Report of the Joint Study Committee Studying (Box 31)
  - Report of the Judicial Council of Virginia (Box 31)
  - Report of the Virginia Commissioners to National Conference on Uniform State Laws to the Governor and the General Assembly of Virginia (Box 31)
  - Report of the Virginia Retirement Study Commission (Box 31)
  - Report on Salary Study (Box 32)
  - Review and Special Audit of the Criminal Fund Payments for the Defense of Indigents (Box 32)
  - Rural Transportation in Southeastern Virginia (Box 32)
  - Rural Public Transportation Feasibility Study (Box 32)
  - Total Transportation Financial Needs During the Next Decade (Box 32)
  - Transportation Commission Briefing Manual (Box 32)
  - Transportation Commission Briefing Manual for Members of the General Assembly (Box 32)
  - Transportation Commission (Box 32)
  - United States Department of Energy (Box 32)
  - Virginia Coal Slurry Pipeline Study (Box 32)
  - Virginia Coal Slurry Pipeline Water Issues (Box 32)
  - Virginia Coal Transportation Study (Box 32)
  - Virginia Climate Advisory (Box 32)
  - Virginia Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (Box 32)
  - Virginia Environment Endowment (Box 33)
  - Virginia Jaycees Governmental Affairs Program (Box 33)
  - Virginia Leading the Way (Box 33)
  - Virginia Newspaper Directory 1986 (Box 33)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (Box 33)
  - Virginia Vital Statistics Annual Report (Box 33)
  - Virginia Uranium Rush--Is it Necessary?? (Box 33)
  - Virginians for Competitive Coal Transportation (Box 33)
  - Voting Assistance Guide 1982 (Box 33)
- Series II-Office Files 1984-1997
  - ABC 1983-1996 (Box 34)